Boys will be boys... but better
Zapped is a tv movie, comedy, family film directed by Peter DeLuise.
Zoey is a talented dancer whose organized life is rudely disrupted when she moves in with her new step-dad and three
step-brothers, until she discovers a dog-training app that can get boys to obey her every command.
But she soon learns that it isn't the cure-all she had hoped for.
Zoey Stevens, played by Zendaya.
Rachel Todds, played by Chanelle Peloso.
Jackson Kale, played by Spencer Boldman.
Taylor Dean, played by Emilia McCarthy.
Adam Thompson, played by Adam DiMarco.
Ben Thompson, played by William Ainscough.
Zapped is a 2014 science fiction teen comedy film
released as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
It stars Zendaya, Chanelle Peloso, Emilia McCarthy and Spencer Boldman.
Zendaya plays the lead role, Zoey Stevens.
The film explores themes of high school, dance,
stepbrother, teen comedy, high school rivalry.
The tone is lighthearted.